https://www.tasty-german-recipe.com/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy
Tasty German Recipe
We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use Tasty German Recipe.com. This document also outlines some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.
Tasty German Recipe strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers', consumers' and online visitors' privacy on our website.
Personal Information
Tasty German Recipe collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name and telephone number.
This information is collected if you request information from us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and sign up to join our email list or request some other service or information from us. The information collected is internally reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries.
Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in our files. If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. Personal information received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties.
Use of Cookies and Web Beacons
We may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize the sites pages, or register with any of our site's services, a cookie enables Tasty German Recipe to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your Web browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.
A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a single website or collection of sites. They are also referred to as web bugs and are commonly used by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic. They may be used in association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a web site.
We may serve third party advertisements that use cookies and web beacons in the course of ads being served on our web site to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. No personally identifiable information you give us is provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information on our web site.
Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions shouldn't cause a problem with our site, should you so choose.
Some third-party advertisements may be provided by Google,
which uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google uses the
DART cookie, which enables it to serve ads to our users based
on their visits to this site and other sites on the Web. You
may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the
Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Google may use interest based advertising where they recognize the types of webpages users visit across the Adsense network.This helps advertisers reach users on the basis of their interests.
California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA)The California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA),
enacted in 2018, creates new consumer rights relating to the access to,
deletion of, and sharing of personal information that is collected by
businesses.We have not sold any personal information in the previous 12 months.Children's Online Privacy Protection Act
This website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.
Non-Personal Information
In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. The information collected is used solely for internal review and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.
Release of Information
If Tasty German Recipe is sold, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of us.
How You Can Correct or Remove Information
We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like that information deleted from our records or would like to update or correct that information, please click use our Contact Us page.
Updates and Effective Date
Creating Invitations reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.
Agreeing to Terms
If you do not agree to Tasty German Recipes Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site.
Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.
Last updated 18th January 2020Return From Privacy Policy To Tasty German Recipe Homepage
HomeRecipe BlogVisitor RecipesDesserts/BakingGerman CookiesChristmasHomemade GiftsMeat RecipesGround BeefTurkeyGerman DrinksGerman Potato SaladPotato RecipesSide DishesSalad RecipesVegetablesSoupsGerman BreadKids RecipesBrotzeitOktoberfest FoodCheese FondueFluent German!Travel GermanyContact MeFree RecipesKitchen StoreFavourite RestaurantsLost RecipesShare This SiteAbout This WebsiteFoodie LinksPrivacy Policy
[?]Subscribe To This Site
Zachary - USA
Tremendous website. I lived in Germany for almost 14 years. Your recipes have me excited about getting back into German cooking. Thanks so much!
How To Make Vanilla SugarMake your own vanilla sugar to use in German cakes, cookies and German dessert recipes.
Copyright 2007-2020 Tasty-German-Recipe.com
